gapbuster.com 2016-11-29

# GBW: Mystery Shopping, Audits, Surveys, Analytics, Consulting

### Privacy Policy

**Disclaimer**  
While GAPbuster Worldwide has endeavoured to ensure that all information provided on the GAPbuster Worldwide internet websites is accurate and up to date, GAPbuster Worldwide takes no responsibility for any errors or omissions relating to this information. To the maximum extent permitted by law, GAPbuster Worldwide will not be held liable for any cost, loss, or damage suffered by you through your use of the GAPbuster Worldwide internet websites or any GAPbuster Worldwide failure to provide access to these internet websites or information updates.

Your use of the websites is governed by the GAPbuster Worldwide website Terms and Conditions of Use

**Online Privacy Policy**  
This online Privacy Policy is provided to make you aware of how GAPbuster Worldwide collects uses and manages information of visitors to its websites.

GAPbuster Worldwide views the personal privacy of users as an important issue and is committed to maintaining the security of personal information provided to GAPbuster Worldwide by users in accessing its' websites.

This policy forms part of the Terms and Conditions of Use of the websites, and describes how GAPbuster Worldwide treats personal information that it receives through your use of the websites.

**What Information Do We Collect and How Is It Used?**  
GAPbuster Worldwide automatically collects the following information regarding visitors to our websites:

  * Your IP address
  * The pages you access
  * Information freely volunteered by you, such as survey information
  * Information freely volunteered by you, in the registration process (refer **Access to GAPbuster Worldwide Portals below)**
  * Specifically, your preferred and nominated means of communication

We do not share your information with any other company or supplier.

GAPbuster Worldwide primarily collects and logs this information for demographic purposes.

GAPbuster Worldwide also uses this information in order to provide you with a personalised experience when you visit our websites. Through the use of a cookie (see below under 'Cookies'), GAPbuster Worldwide can record the pages you visit and the information you require. Through analysis of these records, GAPbuster Worldwide provides you with an improved service when you revisit gapbuster.com.

Other than stated in the preceding paragraphs, no attempt is made to identify users or their browsing activities except in the event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect logs, or where GAPbuster Worldwide believes it is required to collect and produce relevant electronic documentation to fulfil its obligations to third parties, including statutory organizations under local law.

GAPbuster Worldwide endeavours to use and disclose your personal information only in limited circumstances. GAPbuster Worldwide will do so if it is necessary to protect any copyright or intellectual property in the material in the website, or if it is necessary to enforce the GAPbuster website Terms and Conditions of Use.

**Cookies**  
A Cookie is a small data file that websites may write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information, such as a userID, that the website uses to track the pages you have visited. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you personally supply. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites.

Some GAPbuster websites use cookies to track user traffic patterns and to better serve you when you revisit the website. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, providing you with the opportunity to either accept or reject it. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, full functionality for registered members of the GAPbuster Worldwide websites requires the use of cookies.

**Security**  
GAPbuster Worldwide takes all reasonable security measures to protect personal information from loss, unauthorised access, destruction, misuse, modification or disclosure. As far as permissible under law, GAPbuster accepts no responsibility for the unauthorised access of personal information held by GAPbuster Worldwide.

**Access to GAPbuster Worldwide Portals**  
Access to GAPbuster Worldwide Portal websites provides GAPbuster clients and field force with the ability to conduct e-commerce transactions. Users of GAPbuster Portal websites must register with their membership database by providing:

  * E-mail address
  * Name, company name, office name
  * Business/home address, business/home phone
  * Valid GAPbuster internal contact name if relevant
  * Other details as requested

GAPbuster Worldwide will collect details in the membership database that are relevant to the use of the Portal websites. While GAPbuster Worldwide will use the registration details for demographic analysis and to personalise your web experience, GAPbuster Worldwide will not make membership details available to external parties.

**Updating this Privacy Policy**  
The content of this Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, so we suggest that you return to the website on a regular basis and carefully read the information provided.
